<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Optional Rules on DD20 SRD</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/optional-rules/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Optional Rules on DD20 SRD</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/optional-rules/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Modifiers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/optional-rules/modifiers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/optional-rules/modifiers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;modifiers&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Modifiers&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;anchor&#34; href=&#34;#modifiers&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The GM can incorporate any of the following rules adjustments to suit their campaign:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficult Resting&lt;/strong&gt;: When resting, instead of recovering all stress and tags, each player rolls a D20 with no bonus. They can spend boons equal to the result on the &lt;strong&gt;Recover stress&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Recover tags&lt;/strong&gt; options of the &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/reference/#boons&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Boons Table&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Death Roll&lt;/strong&gt;: When a character would become OUT in a context where they might die, the GM can call for a death roll. The player must roll a D20 with no bonus. If they roll a 1, their character dies. If they roll a 20, they recover one stress. If they roll anything else, they become OUT normally.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Side Sheets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/optional-rules/side-sheets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/optional-rules/side-sheets/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;side-sheets&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Side Sheets&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;anchor&#34; href=&#34;#side-sheets&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If the narrative includes an entity such as a character, pet, sidekick, or organization that is important enough to warrant its own character sheet, then the GM can choose to create a side sheet for that character.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As the GM, download or print a &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/downloads/&#34;&gt;side sheet&lt;/a&gt; and fill it out with the following information:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Name&lt;/strong&gt;: The entity&amp;rsquo;s name&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Owners&lt;/strong&gt;: The list of player characters that can make rolls through this side sheet&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stats&lt;/strong&gt;: The list of stats, which could follow the standard rules of character creation or whatever the GM decides&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tags&lt;/strong&gt;: The list of tags, which could follow the standard rules of character creation or whatever the GM decides&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Side sheets do not have experience, drive, or stress. The side sheet&amp;rsquo;s owners can control the entity, roleplay as it, decide its actions, and make rolls through it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tactical Combat</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/optional-rules/tactical-combat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/optional-rules/tactical-combat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;tactical-combat&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Tactical Combat&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;anchor&#34; href=&#34;#tactical-combat&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When starting an action scene, the GM can decide to start a tactical combat, where each combatant is represented by a miniature on a square or hexagonal grid. Tactical combat offers players more ways to deal damage, so GMs can design enemies to be more challenging. All rules for rolling are the same.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If using a square grid, you can move, face, and target orthogonally and diagonally. Miniatures must have a direction they are facing. If it’s not obvious which way the character is facing on the figure itself, please mark its base with a direction.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
