<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>On the Sheet on Double Down SRD</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/character-sheet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in On the Sheet on Double Down SRD</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/character-sheet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Skills</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/character-sheet/skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/character-sheet/skills/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;skills&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Skills&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;anchor&#34; href=&#34;#skills&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Double Down has the following default skills:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agility.&lt;/strong&gt; Represents how quick, nimble, balanced, or stealthy you are. Used to walk tightropes, dodge certain attacks, do parkour, and sneak around.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Charisma.&lt;/strong&gt; Represents how able you are to influence others, whether positively or negatively. Used to persuade, intimidate, and lie.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Combat.&lt;/strong&gt; Represents how trained you are in combat. Used to hunt, spar, and take down enemies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Empathy.&lt;/strong&gt; Represents how attuned you are to others. Used to gain insight into someone else and heal or support them, or interact with animals.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Knowledge.&lt;/strong&gt; Represents your intellect and recall. Used to solve puzzles and remember obscure or important information.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Perception.&lt;/strong&gt; Represents the acuity of your senses. Used to spot clues, search a messy room for a lost item, and see a trap before it springs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Proficiency.&lt;/strong&gt; Represents how practical and technically savvy you are. Used to drive cars, pick locks, and cook a nice meal.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Toughness.&lt;/strong&gt; Represents how physically strong and resilient you are. Used to defend from certain attacks, lift heavy objects, and wrestle.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the nine skills is an intentionally blank field. The GM can determine what this skill is to accommodate the setting. Ask the GM what skill they have selected and write it on the blank skill field on your sheet.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tags</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/character-sheet/tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/character-sheet/tags/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;tags&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Tags&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;anchor&#34; href=&#34;#tags&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;test&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conditions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/character-sheet/conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/character-sheet/conditions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;conditions&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Conditions&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;anchor&#34; href=&#34;#conditions&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Conditions are special narrative status effects that either increase (positive conditions) or decrease (negative conditions) your stars before each roll, and then downgrade after the roll. For example, a positive 3✦ condition called &lt;code&gt;Adrenaline Rush&lt;/code&gt; grants 3✦ to your next roll after acquiring it, then 2✦ to the next roll, and then 1✦ to the next roll. After each roll, erase one star from the condition. To downgrade a negative condition, you must narrate how that specific condition affected your attempt. For example, if you have the negative condition Limping and are trying to attack an enemy, you can describe how your character struggles to maintain their balance (or roleplay it) to downgrade that condition.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stress</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/character-sheet/stress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/character-sheet/stress/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;stress-and-rest&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Stress and Rest&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;anchor&#34; href=&#34;#stress-and-rest&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Stress represents physical injury and hurt morale, with each character taking up to a maximum of ten stress before being out. If you’re out, your character is still alive but cannot attempt or succeed at any rolls until recovered through rest. You cannot recover the stress of a character who is out through boons.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If a character rests for a considerable period of time (8-24 hours) in a non-stressful and safe environment, they rest. When you rest, clear all your stress and negative conditions and recover all your traits.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drive</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/character-sheet/drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/character-sheet/drive/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;regard&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Regard&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;anchor&#34; href=&#34;#regard&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You begin every session with two points of regard. Whenever another player character does something that makes an impression or furthers your relationship with them, whether positively or negatively, you can choose to give them one or more regard. Erase the chosen number of regard from your sheet, and grant them the same amount of drive.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/character-sheet/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/character-sheet/experience/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;experience&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Experience&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;anchor&#34; href=&#34;#experience&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the end of each session, you gain 5 experience points. GMs can grant additional experience points as they see fit as a reward for accomplishing objectives in the campaign.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;During play, you can narrate your character’s training or progress to spend that experience on acquiring new tags or upgrading existing ones. How did they acquire this new tag? For example, you can narrate an arduous training session at a dojo and spend the appropriate amount of experience to upgrade a Martial Arts ability from 2✦ to 3✦. If you are spending experience points to acquire an item/asset, you can for example visit a shop and spend the experience there. For a full list of progression options, see the Experience Table.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
